One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
In My Way
Why did you stop me?
I'm just trying to smash Law's head in!
A clash of Conqueror's Haki!
He can use it too?!
Straw Hatter...
I knew he had it!
Wh-Wh...
What?!
Everyone got knocked out?!
That must be Haki!
"Haki"?
And what's more, it's the Conqueror's Haki!
That's proof that you have the qualities of a king.
Doflamingo!
You're the man chosen by the heavens!
Now...
If you're really a man, then put yourself to the test.
There someone out there you wanna kill?
Do you want me to give you... the strength to take revenge?
People I want to murder...
There's so many!
Doffy's different!
He's of a totally different caliber!
His birth nurtured madness in him!
His fate fed him anger!
Those things turned this man into the perfect demon!
He is no less than the ultimate evil!
I don't give a damn!
Mingo!
Eat this!
Rubber...
Doffy's madness will...
destroy everything!
Eagle...
Bazooka!
Athlete String!
Sticky Stick!
What the hell is this?!
You idiot! Don't think a weakling like you can beat Doffy!
Dammit, let go of me!
Now, Doffy, I'll stall Straw Hat.
Trample Law's head while you have the chance.
Hey! Don't do it, Mingo!
Fight me! Traf can't even move a finger!
I said, "wait for your turn"-
Shut up! This jerk is so icky!
Sticky, not icky!
It's no use!
What?! What's going on?!
If he's a Logia user the Color of Arms should work!
Well then, is my ability really a Logia-type?
Either way, that crap doesn't work against me!
You rubber idiot!
Straw Hatter!
He's right, that won't work on a papier-mâché bastard like him.
P-P-Papier-mâché?!
The main reason I didn't want to sit on the Seat of Hearts...
was because I didn't want to be
lumped together with morons like them!
So you can still move that mouth of yours.
What're you saying, you talking corpse?!
We top commanders are the foundation of the Family!
I'll never forgive anyone for making fun of us!
Sticky-Stick...
Launcher!
Stop! Traf can't even move!
Law, you bastard!
I gotta teach this brat a thing or two!
Move, Doffy!
Listen up, Law!
Doffy will always be the one true king.
However...
We, the current top commanders, are his perfect equals!
That's because...
one day, some thirty years ago,
the four of us acquired this immense gift that fell from the heavens!
We granted him power,
and raised him to be a charismatic force for evil!
You were almost killed in the Holy Land of Mariejoa?
Even after bringing them your father's head?
Even so, I'm glad that you came back alive!
It's a miracle!
Doffy, you have the qualities of a king.
Doffy. We swear to support you in everything.
Doffy, in return, show us your dream.
What's the matter, Doffy?
Where'd you get that wound?
Some hoodlum did this. He should just die.
Okay. I got it.
The hell you want?
Hey, hey, was it you who hurt Doffy?
Oh, that brat.
I just teased him a bit!
What's wrong?
Did somebody hurt you again?
No, I just fell because the road was uneven.
The road? Which town was it?
Oh, I see. This needs to be repaired.
Got it, Doffy?
You're a king.
Rebellion against you is forbidden.
You're the man who will one day...
rule as king of the seas!
We set up Doffy as a king,
and proved his worth to all our subordinates!
But the five of us; Doffy and the top commanders,
all value the family equally,
and we've raised it to its current status!
Like a real family!
Understand, Law?
Do you remember that my mucus is flammable?
I can shut that annoying mouth of yours instant-
"Family"?
It's only you guys who think that, Trebol.
He doesn't give a damn about you guys.
Wh-What did you say?!
How pathetic.
You act like you're his chief of staff, but to me you look like Doflamingo's foolish jester!
F-F-Foolish jester?!
Unforgivable!
Hey, don't fall for it, Trebol!
Room!
You're inside his Room!
This brat is barely alive as it is...
but I've also restrained his movement with my mucus!
What can he do under these circumstances?
Now, open your mouth!
Stop!
You insolent brat!
I'll shove this down your throat and impale you!
Stop!
I'm a ship's captain, too!
If I leave both you and Doflamingo
in Straw Hatter's hands,
I'll lose face!
You can't even move! What can you do?
Damned worm!
Die!
Tact!
What are you-
His arm?!
Sterben!
Blade of Death
4th Step
Flower Field
Is something wrong, Leo?
SMILE Factory
What's the matter, guys?
Everyone's facing the town all of a sudden.
I-I don't know why, but...
I feel like a huge load has been
lifted off my chest...
Hey! We don't have time for that crap!
We finished destroying the factory!
We've gotta get away from the shrinking bird cage!
Royal Palace
What is that?!
This super-skinny old guy
came out of the gooey stuff!
So that's why my punch went right through his body!
Curse you, Law...
You damn fool!
Law...
You die as well!
Oh, shit! He's gonna light us up!
I'm taking you with me!
The Royal Palace burst into flames!
Luffy! Doflamingo is...
Luffyland!
Is he gonna be alright?
We gotta back him up somehow!
I wouldn't do that, if I were you.
Frankly, you might cause him more trouble.
Look! Even Trafalgar Law,
a Warlord of the Sea just like Doflamingo,
has been gravely injured!
Lawland!
Luffy!
Luffy! Send Traf-kun this way!
Robin! Thanks for the help!
Take care of him! Traf's done enough to corner Mingo!
It can't be... his arm!
Cien Fleur: Spider Net!
Hundred Flower: Spider Net
Lawland's arm is...
How terrible...
Traf-kun, stay with me!
Nico Robin!
Don't do anything unnecessary!
He's still breathing.
I haven't dismissed him yet.
Doflamingo!
That bastard's still going for Traf!
I'll finish you off!
Rubber...
Bullet String!
...Hawk Whip!
Damn!
Robiland!
Traf! Robin!
Precious Metal Axe!
Cabbage-kun!
I'm sorry. I just woke up.
Haven't you settled this yet, Straw Hat?!
Cabbage!
Take everyone and get off this plateau!
Don't be absurd!
Doflamingo's standing right here in front of me!
Let me get in at least one hit!
I'm leaving everybody else in your hands!
Le-Leave them in my hands?
Trust...
Respect...
Popularity!
Straw Hat's now my fan.
A fan is asking me a favor...
I can't turn it down!
Bartolomeo should be on the lower level.
Let's use his powers to get down from here!
Can you treat him somehow, Leo?
The cut is ragged.
If I can manage to sew him together...
If you can do that,
I can heal him with my Watering Can.
In any case, we'd better do as Lucy said and head down.
Hey, Bartolomeo!
Make stairs with your barrier!
Zoro-senpai!
Forever!
Are you even listening, you ass?!
That's quite enough,
Straw Hat.
Law is suffering because he can't die.
It's better to put him out of his misery.
If that's what you wanna do, do it after you beat me!
You're looking quite drained out as it is.
Same goes for you!
There's no way all those attacks from Traf left you without a scratch!
Bazooka!
You've definitely got speed, but...
your attacks have no weight to them.
Overheat!
This brings back memories!
Crocodile was defeated?
By a captain from Navy HQ?
Those liars. There must be a catch.
See? It's gotta be him.
His bounty jumped up.
Find out about this crew. I've never heard of them.
Monkey... "D."?
And the Paramount War in which
you fell from the sky!
I can't believe you survived and made it this far!
Wait!
You're awake, Trafalgar!
Leave me... here!
What are you saying?!
For the past thirteen years...
I've stayed alive just to kill Doflamingo.
I've done... everything I can.
I've gotta leave the rest to Straw Hatter.
If he's gonna win,
I want to witness it with my own eyes, here!
If he loses, I need to be here and
die along with him!
I...
got him involved in this fight.
I wanna see this through, right here.
Just leave me!
Trafalgar...
Traf-kun...
Captains in an alliance must be on equal footing.
Luffy is here of his own free will.
He won't fight if he doesn't have the will to do so.
Leave me here...
I'm begging you!
I guess there's no talking you out of it, huh?
Nico Robin, go on ahead.
Cabbage-kun!
I can't abide by a death wish.
I'll stay here, too.
You'll just have to deal with it.
If you're gonna die,
it's gonna be after me.
Robin-senpai!
Robin-san!
Bartolomeo made us stairs!
Go.
Here, take this.
Gear Third!
Rubber...
Grizzly Magnum!
You're wide open!
So you don't wanna let Law's attack go to waste, huh?
How long will it take you...
to take me down?
You know, the one hour time limit...
is the time you have left until the bird cage contracts completely.
I'm sure there are people with bum legs.
There are also the bedridden old people and suckling babies.
Who will be the first victims?
After 30 minutes,
casualties will begin appearing.
After 40 minutes,
we'll start hearing their screams here.
And after 50 minutes,
the whole country will be covered in red, as though tomatoes were crushed.
After an hour, there will not be a single voice left to be heard.
I know that what happens to Dressrosa is none of your concern. However...
Those meeting their end today will
bear grudges against the lot of you.
If only you guys hadn't come here,
Dressrosa could have remained peaceful!
Liar! It only looked that way!
Wherever you go in the world,
you'll always find unfortunate souls.
If you try to save them all, there's no end.
You're just a pirate passing through, and you're gonna play hero?
How dare you stand in my way!
Wrong! You're in my way!
You made my friends cry and my crewmates angry!
But you still haven't gone down,
so I'm taking everything upon myself!
I won't let anybody die!
You and your bird cage are standing in my way!
Gear...
Fourth!